Thank you so much! This is the title track from
our brand new album, Neon Hearts!
I love it!
The city's humming, the lights are low I'm
waiting for you, I'm ready to go The rain is
tapping on the glass I knew this feeling was
built to last I hear footsteps in the hall I'm not
afraid to fall This is the only thing I know is
true You got my knee and heart Shining for you in
the dark The love so bright it's self-adjust You
got my neon heart It's an electric color feeling
And it all starts with you
We're walking fast on the wet concrete The
rhythm matches when our eyes meet Don't need a
promise, don't need a vow My only moment is right
here, right now I hear your footsteps in the hall
I'm not afraid to fall This is the only thing I
know is true You've got my neon heart Shining for
you in the dark A love so bright it's off the
charts You've got my neon heart It's an electric
color feeling And it all starts with you
Let the city sleep, we're wide awake A chance
that we're both gonna take
You got my neon heart shining for you in the dark.
A love so bright it's off the charts. You've got
my neon heart. It's an electric color feeling,
and it all starts with you. My neon heart.
Money on top Hey!